bestbuygames.com 2015-11-14

# Iplay Download Games Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to iWin. IWin operates various websites with game-related products and services (our "Sites") and provides applications for the provision of various online and mobile services, such as search and gaming (collectively, "Applications") through which personal information may be collected. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to all personal information collected by iWin through our Sites and Applications.

If iWin is operating the Sites or Applications under an agreement with a specific partner, the branding of the Site or the Application will indicate the specific partner with which iWin operates the Site or Application ("Identified Partners"). In such an event, iWin may share the data collected with that particular identified Partner. Accordingly, iWin's use of your data is subject to our Privacy Policy - and our Identified Partner's use of your data is subject to its privacy policy. You should familiarize yourself with such Identified Partner's privacy policy. Some of iWin's Identified Partners serve their own ads or use other ad-serving networks. To opt out of data collection by an Identified Partner's ad-serving network, please see that Identified Partner's privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding the information collected online through Sites and Applications maintained by iWin, and not to websites or services offered and operated by other companies or organizations to which we link. Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not cover information that we collect through other methods, such as mail-in sweepstakes.

IWin is headquartered in the United States and the collected data is stored in the United States. Although we operate Sites and maintain some operations outside the United States, when you become a member of one of our online communities or programs, make a purchase from iWin or register for one of the Applications, your account is with a United States company and your data will be stored in the United States. By registering and using this Site, Members acknowledge that the processing of their personally identifying information for the purposes described above may involve the transfer of such personally identifying information from within the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as stringent as that within the European Union.

BY USING THIS SITE, APPLICATION, OR USING ANY OF THE RELATED SERVICES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO IWIN'S PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR UNDERSTANDING THAT IWIN MAY PROCESS YOUR DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE FOREGOING, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR APPLICATION OR IF ALREADY A MEMBER YOU MUST TERMINATE YOUR ACCOUNT.

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

If you are a visitor to a Site or a user of an Application, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly provide us with on an individual basis ("Personal Information") and statistical and usage information collected using cookies and other technologies as you browse the Site or use an Application ("Usage Information").

### 1\. Personal Information

#### Registration Information

You will need to provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your preferences when you register on one of the Sites or for one of the Applications. The specific information collected will vary depending on the Site or Application, and may include your name, email address, username (or player name), postal address, telephone number, birth date, and gender. Registration is not required to browse any of our Sites, but you will not be able to view certain content or use aspects of certain Sites or Applications that require registration if you do not provide the requested information.

#### Credit Card Information

If you choose to purchase products or services from us or our partners, you may need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number. iWin securely transmits Credit Card Information to our payment processor for verification and processing. In some instances, iWin also securely stores your encrypted credit card information. For all transactions, iWin employs secure servers and the secure server software (SSL) to encrypt all payment information. In all instances, iWin has made a substantial investment in server, database, backup, and firewall technologies to protect the assets of the Site, including the confidentiality of information collected about Members. These technologies are deployed as part of a sophisticated security architecture and protocol.

#### Email Information

In addition to providing us with your email address as part of registration, if you choose to correspond with us via email or by using a web interface to reach customer support, we may retain the content of your messages together with your email address and our responses.

### 2\. Usage Information

Similar to other commercial websites, we utilize standard technologies such as "cookies," clear GIFs (also known as "web beacons" or "action tags") and web server logs to collect information about how the Sites and Applications are used. Additionally, when you connect to or download an Application, we may retrieve information from the computer used to log onto the Application. The information we collect may include technical information about your computer, system and application software, and peripherals, and any data related to the use and operation of the software used in connection with the Application.

#### Cookies

As an important and necessary part of providing customizable and personalized services to our Members, iWin sites or its advertisers may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to store and sometimes track non-personal information about Members while on the Website. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a Member's browser from a Web server and stored on a Member's computer hard drive. Areas of iWin sites where Members are prompted to log in or that are customizable require acceptance of cookies. These technologies are also used to help iWin track the response to messages sent to Members on the part of marketers so that iWin can monitor and report campaign results to the marketer and track response history and campaign effectiveness. In addition, banner advertisements are displayed on our websites which may contain certain cookies. While iWin uses cookies in other parts of our websites, the cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertising partners, and iWin does not have access to this information. Members may opt out of the advertising that they see on our sites targeted specifically to them by going to the respective sites' privacy policy(ies) and following directions. To opt out of Google's "interest-based ads" and to learn more about Google's collection of personal information to serve ads in connection with iWin, please go to www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/. With respect to cookies, users have a choice. By modifying their browser preferences, they have the choice to accept all cookies; they will be unable to use those iWin services that require the use of cookies in order to participate.

#### Clear GIFs

Clear GIFs are small, invisible graphic images (usually only one pixel) placed on a web page or email message to capture statistical usage information. They are not used to collect personal information about you.

#### IP Addresses

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer every time you are connected to the internet. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that appropriate data (such as the web pages you request) and geographically relevant content can be sent to you.

### ADVERTISING

#### Our Advertisers

IWin's advertisers and advertising vendors display targeted advertisements. Although we do not provide any personal information to the advertiser or advertising vendor, by interacting with or clicking on an ad you acknowledge the possibility that the advertiser may assume you meet the targeting criteria used.

In addition to cookies placed by iWin or its agents as described above, advertisers and advertising vendors that serve ads onto our Sites may use their own cookies or other tracking technologies. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such advertisers and vendors.

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

#### Uses of your Personal Information

IWin will use your information primarily to provide you with our products and services and to receive payment from you. In order to do this, we may determine whether you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products. We may also ask you to participate in surveys about products, services, news, and events; we may offer you product upgrades and games for you to purchase. You may opt out of some of these uses.

IWin may also provide Personal Information to companies we engage as contractors or agents to perform services for us, such as maintaining software, providing email marketing, or administering a sweepstakes or contest. Information will be shared with contractors only to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations. Members should note that iWin may change this Policy at any time, and therefore iWin may in the future store some information for additional purposes not currently included in this policy.

#### Uses of Usage Information

Usage Information may be used by iWin to analyze Site and Application use in order to optimize the Site and the Applications and improve the user experience. iWin may use the information collected from your computer related to technical aspects of your connecting to a Site or Application in order to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support, and other services to you (if any) related to the Sites and Applications, to verify compliance with the terms of the applicable Site or Application, to improve our products or services or to provide Services or technologies to you.

### GENERALLY

#### Where is the information held?

We are a global organization and the computer systems on which we collect, store, and use the information collected or received are based in the United States and elsewhere. Your personal information may be transferred to , used, processed, or held by IWin in the United States and in other countries, including both member and non-member countries of the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

#### Third-Party Disclosure of Personal Information

IWin does not use your Personal Information for the purposes incompatible with those listed above. Other than as provided in this Privacy Policy, iWin does not provide your Personal information to third parties unless you specifically consent to provide such information to a third party. Sometimes, certain indirectly identifiable information needs to be communicated with third-party vendors, for example, to process an order you have made. We may also disclose Personal Information when legally compelled to do so. In other words, when the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary or appropriate to address potential or actual injury or interference with the rights, property, or operations or iWin, our users or others. Finally, if we undergo a merger or acquisition, or sell or otherwise transfer substantially all the assets of iWin, or relating to any website that we own or operate or any product or service that we offer, Personal Information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

#### Selected Notifications

Occasionally we may also use the information we collect to notify you about new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. We will send you this type of communication only if we have received your permission to do so.

#### How Does IWin Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?

We use industry standard technology and services to protect and secure your information. We will never initiate any email communication with you that requests your private information beyond the purposes of user identification for support. In general, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Please contact iWin support if you have any questions or concerns.

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection

The safety of children is important to us. IWin's websites are for a general audience that is not directed to children under the age of 18. Similarly, iWin's services are not directed to or intended for anyone under the age of 18. IWin will not knowingly accept members who are under the age of 18 years nor will it knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from or about anyone under the age of 18 years. IWin relies on the truthfulness of the registration when accepting new Members. In the event that iWin receives information that establishes that a Member is under the age of 18 years, iWin reserves the right, but not the obligation, to terminate that Member's membership or take other steps that it determines are appropriate in the circumstances, such as providing parental notification. IWin may also delete all information in our databases about that terminated Member.

#### Employee Access, Training, and Expectations

Our corporate values, ethical standards, and practices are committed to the appropriate protection of customer and visitor information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes, and transactions. This obligation continues once an employee has left our company.

#### What About Other Websites Linked to Our Website?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Sites or accessed through our Applications, nor the information or content contained in any search results or third-party websites. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be of interest to the users of our Sites and Applications. Please remember that when you use a link to go from a Site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on one of our Sites, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### Your Consent

By using any of our Sites or Applications, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Modification of Privacy Policy by IWin

IWin reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by positing a notice that we are changing this Privacy Policy. If there is a change to this Privacy Policy, we will post the change on the Site or with the Application to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. You will be deemed to have accepted such change if you continue to use the Site or Application after the new policy has been posted. In the event that this document conflicts in any way with the User Agreement, the User Agreement shall take precedence over the relationship.

Effective: June 25, 2014
